<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PimpMyLaser</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">
        This app should give you an estimate of the height of an object by calculating\n
        its height from two values: The distance to the objects top and the angle to the\n
        objects top.\n
        This app is intended to be used with a laser rangefinder.\n
        This app comes withouth any kind of warranty implied.\n
        If you die because of this app i dont care.\n
        The accurance of this app depends on your phone sensors. On Android phones, the sensor\n
        accurancy varies from phone model to phone model. On some phones this app might not work.\n
        <b>How to use</b>\n
        1. click on next below\n
        2. point the top of your phone slightly up. The displayed angle should increase.\n
        3. put your laser on the marking on the phone, so laser and phone top point at the same spot\n
        4. measure the distance to the top spot you want to measure\n
        5. while keeping the top spot in the lasers center, click "save angle" on your phone\n
        6. enter the distance your laser measured\n
        7. this app should give you an approximate height of the object. the more accurate you \n
        point, the more accurate the reading.\n
        8. the last measured values can be checked in the menue: just select last measurements there.\n
        <b>For better results</b>\n
        This app is using your phones magnetometer. it wont be accurate with strong magnetic fields close.
        Dont use close to power lines, speakers, strong magnetic fields.\n
        Measure multiple times. the whole measuring process is pretty error prone. You might tilt your phone while trying
        to hit the "save angle" button or you might have hit the wrong spot with your laser or you might have moved your laser on the phone surface while
        trying to measure. Use both hands.

        <b>always throw multiple rocks to be shure.</b>
    </string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="current_angle">Current Angle: %1$.2f</string>
    <string name="calculated_height">Calculated Height: %1$.2f</string>
    <string name="save_distance_button">SAVE DISTANCE</string>
    <string name="distance_input_label">Enter measured distance:</string>
    <string name="go_measure">Go Measure</string>
    <string name="show_last">Show last</string>
    <string name="delete_all_measurements">delete all measurements</string>
    <string name="show_instructions">show Instructions</string>
</resources>
